<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Will Hick&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Will Hick&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>B&amp;Q, GXO, and My VR Journey</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/bq-gxo-vr-journey/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/bq-gxo-vr-journey/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today was genuinely exciting. B&amp;amp;Q and GXO brought two trainers and a hiring manager to campus alongside a full tractor unit. We could ask questions, take photos, and discuss VR training. They&amp;rsquo;re clearly interested in what I&amp;rsquo;m building.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;historic-passion-for-vr&#34;&gt;Historic Passion for VR&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinated by VR. The idea of immersive, simulated environments stuck with me long before it became mainstream. When the Final Year Project came around, I knew I wanted this to be my focus. It&amp;rsquo;s one thing to follow a trend, another to genuinely care about the technology and its potential applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Secretary of Tech Connect</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tech-connect-secretary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tech-connect-secretary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This academic year, I&amp;rsquo;m serving as Secretary for Tech Connect, a new society I cofounded with two others after being invited. It&amp;rsquo;s been rewarding to help build something from the ground up.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;what-is-tech-connect&#34;&gt;What is Tech Connect?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A student-led networking society bridging the gap between students and tech companies. Our mission: get companies to network with students and vice versa. Building connections and understanding how companies operate is invaluable for students entering the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Third Year of University</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/third-year-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/third-year-university/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve made it to third year. The journey has been solid so far. I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot and despite some struggles, I feel I&amp;rsquo;m on the right track academically. My career prospects are a different story though. The tech industry is challenging right now and securing a good internship or graduate scheme has proven more difficult than expected.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not landing any summer internships or placements last year was a setback for my confidence. I&amp;rsquo;ve been working to rebuild it and refocus on my studies, but it&amp;rsquo;s challenging when the competition is fierce and it seems like everyone else has more experience and better connections.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
