<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Will Hick&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Will Hick&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thrilled to Announce... We Still Need a Real Network for Musicians</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/market-analysis-of-musician-networking-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/market-analysis-of-musician-networking-apps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;linkedin&#34;&gt;LinkedIn&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately for everyone, LinkedIn is a dominant force in the wonderful world of corporate capitalism. It&amp;rsquo;s a behemoth of networking, considered invaluable and a bare minimum requirement to progress your career in any remotely techy or financey field, and is genuinely a very well made product. You have to hand it to them, the infinite scroll of self-congratulation and vague buzzwords is remarkably addictive.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;LinkedIn was rather unceremoniously born in the living room of one Reid Hoffman, ex-founder of the now defunct SocialNet.com alongside his various colleagues of his various jobs in tech, quickly transforming from a simple idea to the professional world&amp;rsquo;s favourite digital water cooler. LinkedIn&amp;rsquo;s team quickly realised people didn&amp;rsquo;t just want to network, they wanted opportunities and to brag about their lives in the hopes of opening up more opportunities, with it now transcending into the number one place where every newgrad claims their two-week-long ultimate expertise in whatever is the current JavaScript framework of the hour after completing chapter 1 of a Udemy course.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening Words</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The original version of this post was rather wet and soppy, and if you go hunting through this repo I&amp;rsquo;m sure you can find it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Tl:dr, this is gonna be where I write my thoughts. I&amp;rsquo;m not good at it, but I&amp;rsquo;m trying to do better, and hopefully it&amp;rsquo;ll help me out in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This being public is just a bonus, I guess.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ciao&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
