<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Will Hick&#39;s Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Will Hick&#39;s Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DITHERMAN</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/ditherman/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/ditherman/</guid>
      <description>I basically made this project because I found an app called Dither Boy and didn&amp;rsquo;t really feel like paying for it. As much as I applaud indie studios like this for trying to make a neat piece of software all in one, the concept isn&amp;rsquo;t exactly novel and not particularly hard to replicate, however Dither Boy is absolutely a much better product. From just the videos I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it&amp;rsquo;s faster, can do videos and gifs, and applies the dithering effects much better.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PLOTCYPHER</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/plotcypher/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/plotcypher/</guid>
      <description>This was my first big project I completed. It&amp;rsquo;s a React based daily media guessing game in the same vain as Wordle. It&amp;rsquo;s not particularly good, I was learning at this stage. Looking back there are a lot of changes I would make.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thrilled to Announce... We Still Need a Real Network for Musicians</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/market-analysis-of-musician-networking-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/market-analysis-of-musician-networking-apps/</guid>
      <description>LinkedIn Unfortunately for everyone, LinkedIn is a dominant force in the wonderful world of corporate capitalism. It&amp;rsquo;s a behemoth of networking, considered invaluable and a bare minimum requirement to progress your career in any remotely techy or financey field, and is genuinely a very well made product. You have to hand it to them, the infinite scroll of self-congratulation and vague buzzwords is remarkably addictive.&#xA;LinkedIn was rather unceremoniously born in the living room of one Reid Hoffman, ex-founder of the now defunct SocialNet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Opening Words</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/intro/</guid>
      <description>Hi,&#xA;The original version of this post was rather wet and soppy, and if you go hunting through this repo I&amp;rsquo;m sure you can find it.&#xA;Tl:dr, this is gonna be where I write my thoughts. I&amp;rsquo;m not good at it, but I&amp;rsquo;m trying to do better, and hopefully it&amp;rsquo;ll help me out in the long run.&#xA;This being public is just a bonus, I guess.&#xA;Ciao</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
